Contact

6361563076 (Mobile) query@pranavms.ml

www.linkedin.com/in/pranavms13 (LinkedIn) pranavms.ml (Personal)

Top Skills

Cryptocurrency
Python (Programming Language)
Cryptocurrency Developer

Languages

Kannada (Native or Bilingual)
Tamil (Elementary)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) Python

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4

Machine Learning

Blockchain Essentials

Learn Python by Building a Blockchain & Cryptocurrency

Pranav M S

Competition Contributer at Kaggle

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

I grew up in Bangalore, India.

Currently pursuing Computer Science Engineering in K S Institute of Technology. Deeply Interested in Developing applications. I started coding at the age of 10. Started many hobby projects and later worked as a Lead Developer for a Proof-Of-Work Based Cryptocurrency "ReCoal" at the age of 17.

My interests also include Web Development, Mobile App Development, IoT Based Automation, CyberSecurity Application Development.

Experience

Kaggle Competition Contributer October 2019 - Present

Verzeo ML Developer July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Completed Internship at Verzeo.

Education

KS Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)